Papers of Diane Wakoski circa 1959-1980 (bulk 1959-1978)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VIII: Manuscripts, additional records, 1960-1980, undated
  - Subseries 2: Other works
    - Magicians Feast Letter, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Titled, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Yugoslavian Works, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - About the New Poetry, part 1, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - About the New Poetry, part 2, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - About the New Poetry, sections, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - About Interviews, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Articles, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Greed 10: 1st Notebook, pp. 1-57, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Greed 10: 1st Notebook, pp. 58-110, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Greed 10: 2nd Notebook, pp. 111-174, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Greed 10: 2nd Notebook, pp. 175-253, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Greed 10: 3rd Notebook, pp. 254-331, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Greed 10: 3rd Notebook, pp. 332-383, undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Part 1, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Part 2, undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Part 3, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Part 4, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Part 5, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Part 6, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Part 7, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Magellenic Clouds, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - The Man Who Shook Hands, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - The Motorcycle Betrayal Poems: Personal Manuscript, circa 1970 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - The Motorcycle Betrayal Poems: Publisher’s Manuscript, circa 1970 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - The Natural Community, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Smudging: Final Personal Manuscript, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Virtuoso Literature for Two and Four Hands, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Notebook: 1962, part 1 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: 1962, part 2 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: 1964-1968, part 1 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: 1964-1968, part 2 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: 1964-1968, part 3 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Notebook: 1970 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Notebook: 1971, part 1 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Notebook: 1971, part 2 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Notebook: undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Notebook: Envelope to Lauren Shakely, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Notebook: Envelope in box, undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Notebook: Play script, undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Notebook: NBP/Greed 5, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Notebook: Other Items: “This Beautiful Black Marriage”, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Notebook: Poems for the Buddha’s Birthday/Uncollected Poems, part 1, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: Poems for the Buddha’s Birthday/Uncollected Poems, part 2, undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: Uncollected Poems/Poems for the Buddha’s Birthday/Uncollected Poems, part 3, undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: Student/Early, part 1, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: Student/Early, part 2, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Notebook: Student/Early, part 3, undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Notebook: Smudging, part 1, undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Notebook: Smudging, part 2, undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Notebook: Smudging, part 3, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Notebook: Various Collection, part 1, undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Notebook: Various Collection, part 2, undated (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Notebook: Various Collection, part 3, undated (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Notebook: Various Collection, part 4, undated (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Notebook: Various Collection, part 5, undated (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Notebook: Various Collection, part 6, undated (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Notebook: Various notes, undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Series IX: Works by Others, 1960-1980, undated
  - Allen, Dick: Anon and Various Time Machine Poems, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Jack: The Invention of New Jersey, undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Jane H.: Poem in Progress, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Arvon Foundation, undated (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Autobiography, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Bell, Richard: Poems, undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Bennett, Beth, undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Berryhill, Michael: First Light, undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Bisbee Poetry Festival, circa 1980 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Bloedow, undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Borenstein, undated (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Bursk, Christopher, undated (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Carroll, Jonathan: Stories, undated (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Cash, Jim, undated (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Coleman, Mary, undated (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Concept Art, undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Diouysus, undated (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Dowden, George, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Evans, Dalene, undated (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - The Falcon, undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Falleur, Barbara: To Find the Bridge, undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Foreman, Richard, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Garrett, George, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Georgia Review, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Goodell, Larry, undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Gorlin, Debra, undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Greenberg, Alvin (Al): Metaform; In/Direction, undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Grossberg, undated (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Halmos, P.R.: Mathematician, undated (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Hand, J.C., undated (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Hejinian, undated (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Heyen, William, undated (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Hepworth, James R., undated (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Hornick, Lila, undated (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Housing, undated (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Hulbert, Joyce, undated (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Ivask, Astrio: Autumn in the Cascade Mountains, undated (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Job Inquiries, undated (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Johnson, Judith (Judith Johnson Sherwin): How the Dead Count, undated (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Kaminsky, Marc: Birthday Poems/Berkeley Poems, undated (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Kelleher, Ann C.: Five Canticles; Northeaster, undated (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Kelmachter, Mark, undated (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Larsen, undated (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Lopez, Barry: River Notes, undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Lord, Mae Maskit and Stone, Carole; About Diane, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Martin, Herbert W: The Shit-Storm Poems, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Macho Poetry, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - The Managed World, undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Meiners, undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Merians, Linda: The Madness of the Mazy Dance; Augustan Tradition and the Dunciad, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Miller, Stephen, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Mock, John R. That Blast of Orange Full Fire Two Hours Away from Dark, undated (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Mood, John, undated (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Murphy, Paul, undated (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Olson, Toby: the Life of Jesus (excerpts), undated (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Openheimer, Joel, undated (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Parrish, Wendy: The Perfect Native, undated (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Pasquale, Emanuel D.: Genesis, undated (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Paval, John, undated (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Povich, Anita: Dreams of Hilliard, The Importance of Ritual, undated (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Rollings, Alan: Transparent Landscapes, undated (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome: Poland/1931, undated (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Schmidt, Eric: Various writings, undated (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Sheila?, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Sinclair, Margorie, undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Sealock, Robert, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Lawrence R. “Vibrio Book 1”, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Stone Dream: Review of D.W. Motorcycle Betrayal Poems, circa 1970 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Stover, Virginia: Looking for the King of Spain; A Feminist View of the Poetry of Diane Wakoski, undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Tourtelot, Madeline, undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - UA Arts Competition, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Urrea, Luis, undated (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Vas Dias, Robert: Speech Acts and Happenings, undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Various Students, undated (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - A-G, undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - K-R, undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - S-Z, undated (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Vawter, Linda, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Viereck, Peter, undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Wagner, Linda: Personism, undated (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Weinberger, Eliot: Montemora and Kathmandu, undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Weinberger, Tony: Prose, undated (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Weinstein, Norman: Poems, undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Weller, Sheila: To Be a Poet, Diane Wakoski’s New Poems, A Mellow Homecoming, Poems, undated (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Wild, Peter: Cochise, undated (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Williamson, Ellen: Book of Poems (No Title Page), undated (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Yandall, Eric, undated (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Yates, David, undated (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Young, La Monte and Zazeela, Marian, undated (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Yugoslavia poetry by various poets, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Series X: Miscellaneous Information, additional information, 1960-1980, undated
  - Seminars, Readings, Conferences, undated (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Travel, undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Material, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings about Bisbee Poetryfest, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Series XI: Personal Journals, 1966-1984,undated
  - 1966-1971 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - 1970-1985 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Circa 1975 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Circa 1980 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Circa 1984 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Undated; undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - AV material: Readings, etc. (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Series XII: Chapbooks and Journals, 1955-1978
  - A-L, 1950-1978 (Box 86)
  - M-Z, 1955-1978 (Box 87)